Guide to the Amos Niven Wilder and Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Amos Niven Wilder Papers, 1860–2014; Series III
  - Personal papers, 1896–1996
    - Education and related materials
      - University of Chicago materials, 1943–1955 (Box 34, Folder 551)
        Includes correspondence and typescript writings.
      - Wedding materials, 1935–1968 (Box 34, Folder 552-553)
        Includes notes from the weddings of Amos Tappan Wilder and Robin Gibbs, Sarah Kerlin and William Barton Gray, and Amos Niven Wilder and Catharine Kerlin. Includes materials from the wedding of Sarah Kerlin and William Barton Gray in 1965 and Gilbert Kerlin and Sarah Morrison in 1941. Also includes undated notes from Jenney Kerlin's memorial service.
      - Yale materials, 1956–1964 (Box 34, Folder 554)
      - Yale scholarship record, circa 1920 (Box 34, Folder 555)
    - Personal scrapbooks and diaries
      - Oxford scrapbook, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 556)
        Includes postcards and photographs collected during Amos's time at Balioll College, Oxford.
      - Brussels and Oxford diary, 1921–1922 (Box 34, Folder 557)
      - Mansfield Lectures, 1921–1922 (Box 34, Folder 558)
        Includes lectures by W. Selbie from January to June, 1922 and includes a lecture list for Michaelmas term.
      - Schweitzer, Albert and Dale lectures, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 559)
        Diary from Albert Schweitzer's lectures at Oxford and Dale lectures at Mansfield College in February 1922.
      - Selbie lectures, 1921–1922 (Box 34, Folder 560)
      - Plan de Bruxelles et la Grande Banlieue, undated (Box 34, Folder 561)
      - Map of Mons- Luxembourg, undated (Box 34, Folder 562)
      - Sermons, Ecchinswell, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 563)
      - Journal, 1922–1923 (Box 35, Folder 564)
        Travel diary from Amos's time in Florence, Italy.
      - Diaries, 1924–1928 (Box 35, Folder 565-570)
      - Record, 1943–1949 (Box 35, Folder 571-572)
      - Class records, 1943–1968 (Box 35, Folder 573-582, Box 36, Folder 584-587)
      - Journal: family in Europe, Frankfurt, Geneva, 1952–1953 (Box 36, Folder 588)
      - Notes, diary, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 589)
      - Planner, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 590)
      - Journal and notes, Chicago and Paris, 1939–1944 (Box 36, Folder 591)
      - Record, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 592)
      - Journal, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 593)
      - Family log and lecture notes, circa 1966 (Box 36, Folder 594)
      - Diary, with family information in the back, circa 1967 (Box 36, Folder 595)
      - Address book, small, undated (Box 36, Folder 596)
      - Address book, large, undated (Box 37, Folder 597)
      - Notebook, 1919–1920 (Box 37, Folder 598)
        Includes family correspondence and notes.
      - Diary, 1919 February (Box 37, Folder 599)
        Yale University notebook with loose pages.
      - Montauban lectures, 1919 April 5 (Box 37, Folder 600)
        Includes a letter written to Pierre Veber.
      - The Self Book, undated (Box 37, Folder 601)
      - Record, 1949–1950 (Box 37, Folder 602)
      - Record, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 603)
      - Diary and notes, Frankfurt, 1953 January (Box 37, Folder 604)
      - Diary, 1955 November - December 1955 (Box 38, Folder 605)
      - Notes, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 606)
      - Course at the University of Frankfurt, 1952–1953 (Box 38, Folder 607)
        Notebook from a course on English and American poets.
      - Harvard Magazine, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 608)
      - Wilder, Charlotte correspondence, 1916–1953 (Box 38, Folder 609)
        Includes Charlotte's correspondence, an apartment lease, and The Mount Holyoke.
      - Wilder, Charlotte articles, 1925–1937 (Box 38, Folder 610)
        Includes The World Tomorrow, The Mount Holyoke Monthly, and The Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarterly featuring Charlotte's articles.
      - Charlotte E. Wilder journal and correspondence, 1926–1953 (Box 38, Folder 611)
      - Imagining the Real materials, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 612-613)
        Includes Charlotte's poetry.
      - "A Brief Centennial History of the Minister's Club in Boston" materials, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 614)
      - Society for Values in Higher Education Directory of Fellows, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 615)
      - "Eloges Prononces lors de l'Audience Publique du Tribunal de Premiere Instance de Tournai", 1972–1974 (Box 39, Folder 616)
        A pamphlet from an event held in memory of M. Jule Deschamps. Also included is a postcard from an unknown correspondent.
      - Memorial Service programs, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 617)
        Includes two copies of the memorial service program for Amos held on June 21, 1993.
      - Memorial Service paperwork, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 618)
        Includes correspondence, invitation list, and photocopied readings from the memorial service.
      - "Vignettes of Men Memorialized in the buildings of the Yale Divinity School", 1956–1989 (Box 39, Folder 619, Box 69, Folder 833, Box 181, Folder 2411a)
        Written by Roland H. Bainton and includes Some Annals of the Yale Christian Association. Also includes two oversized folders which contain a William Lyon Phelps Lecture and a copy of the Yale Daily News dated October 21, 1959.
      - 50th reunion- class of 1917 materials, circa 1967 (Box 39, Folder 620)
      - Centennial Days: A Chronicle, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 621)
      - Harvard Daily Bulletin, 1965 January (Box 39, Folder 622)
      - Oberlin College- Class of 1917 materials, circa 1937-1982 (Box 39, Folder 623-624)
      - Hermann Dumont, Echevin, In Memoriam, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 625)
      - Root, Edward W. catalog, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 626)
      - "Some Annals of the Yale Christian Association", 1937 (Box 39, Folder 627)
      - "Facts: The Story of a Seminary", circa 1943 (Box 39, Folder 628)
      - Benjamin Wisner Bacon: Pioneer in American Biblical Criticism and reviews, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 629)
      - Notes, undated (Box 39, Folder 630)
      - Notes on deconstruction, undated (Box 39, Folder 631)
        Fragmented notes written in Amos's hand.
      - Toulouse- Montauban journal (Box 39, Folder 632)
      - Old writings, Ex-Soldier sermons, 1926; undated (Box 39, Folder 633)
        Includes Our Lost Millennium, The Lesson of the Fallen, The Ex-Solider, Ambassadors of the Fallen, and The Resurrection of the Fallen. Includes both handwritten and typescript copies of the articles.
      - Wilder records, mostly letters to ANW overseas, 1916–1920 (Box 39, Folder 634)
      - Wilder family history materials, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 636)
        Typescript of a family history written by Amos.
      - Otherwordliness and the New Testament reviews and other materials, 1953–1956 (Box 41, Folder 637)
      - Ann Arbor lectures, 1956–1957 (Box 41, Folder 638)
      - Kenyon College lecture, circa 1970 (Box 41, Folder 639)
      - Certificates, appointments, credits, and courses taken, 1921–1953 (Box 41, Folder 640)
        Includes course identification cards for the Universite libre de Bruxelles and the Universite catholique de Louvain and certificates from Johann Wolgang Goethe- Universitat and the University of Toulouse, France.
      - Family notes, 1946–1954 (Box 41, Folder 641)
      - 95th birthday cards, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 642-643)
      - Egypt and Middle East trip materials, 1919–1925 (Box 41, Folder 644-645)
      - Harvard appointment letters, 1954–1980 (Box 41, Folder 646)
        Includes clippings, notes, and correspondence.
      - Family notes, 1946–1954 (Box 41, Folder 647-648)
      - World War I related clippings, circa 1918 (Box 41, Folder 649)
      - Passports, 1922–1975 (Box 41, Folder 650)
    - Printed materials
      - Reviews and printed articles, 1946–1964 (Box 42, Folder 651)
      - Reviews and printed articles, 1964–1986 (Box 42, Folder 652)
      - Printed materials, 1951–1980 (Box 42, Folder 653-661)
        Includes Christian, alumni, and literary publications in English and German,
      - Semeia, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 662)
      - Racquet, 1988–1991 (Box 43, Folder 663-666)
  - Catharine Kerlin Wilder materials, 1916–1985
    - Address book, circa 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 667-668)
    - General correspondence, 1924–1966 (Box 43, Folder 669-670)
    - Kerlin, Jenney correspondence, 1924–1966 (Box 43, Folder 671)
    - Kerlin, Jenney suffrage pins and pennants, 1916–1920 (Box 44)
      Includes suffrage pins and pennants owned by Catharine's mother, Jenney. The pins included are seven votes for women pins, a delegate's pin from the Suffrage Convention in Atlantic City and a delegate's ribbon from the Victory Convention in Newark, a pin depicting Lucy Stone, and a medal from the Jubilee Convention of NAWSA in 1920 in Chicago.
    - Miscellaneous files, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 672)
    - Passports, 1937–1985 (Box 43, Folder 674, Box 45, Folder 675-676)
      Includes both Amos and Catharine's passports.
    - Wills, 1958–1966 (Box 45, Folder 677-678)
    - Writings, 1959–1967 (Box 45, Folder 679)
    - Correspondence
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 680-681)
      - Guiles, Catharine Dix Wilder, 1958–1976 (Box 45, Folder 682-683)
      - Wilder, Amos Niven, 1939–1974 (Box 45, Folder 684)
      - Wilder, Amos Niven memorial service announcement, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 685)
      - Wilder, Amos Tappan, 1958–1959 (Box 45, Folder 686)
      - Wilder, Charlotte, 1969–1971 (Box 45, Folder 687)
      - Wilder, Isabel, 1952–1982 (Box 45, Folder 688-691, Box 46, Folder 692-693)
      - Wilder, Isabella, 1937–1944 (Box 46, Folder 694-695)
    - Personal scrapbooks and photographs
      - California loose photographs, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 696)
        Includes photographs from Amos and Catharine's travels to the Thacher School and along the California coast.
      - Claremont, California scrapbook, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 703-706, Box 48, Folder 707-710)
      - European travel diary, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 697-702)
      - Houston travel diary, 1963 January (Box 49, Folder 711)
      - India and Near East travel files, circa 1925 (Box 49, Folder 712-714)
        Includes photographs and palm leaves with inscriptions.
      - Kerlin family scrapbook, circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 715)
      - New Harmony, Indiana scrapbook, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 731-734)
        Includes clippings from Amos' lecture tour.
      - Photograph album, Blue Hill, Maine, 1935–1982 (Box 49, Folder 716-720, Box 50, Folder 721-727)
        These folders consist mainly of family photographs from Blue Hill, Maine. The album itself was received by the library in poor condition and most of the photographs were coming out of their enclosed photo album pages. Each grouping of photographs was previously one photograph album page. The album also includes slides.
      - Photograph album, 1964–1969 (Box 52)
      - Photograph album, 1935–1939 (Box 40)
        Includes photographs from Amos and Catharine's engagement party, wedding, and honeymoon.
      - Rice University scrapbook, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 736-741, Box 54, Folder 742-746)
        Includes material from a scrapbook documenting Amos and Catharine's time during which Amos was a guest lecturer at Rice University.
      - Russian trip scrapbook and materials (Box 50, Folder 728-729)
        Includes an itinerary, plane ticket, map, notes, and blank postcards from Catharine's trip to Russia.
    - Sabbatical scrapbooks
      - Sabbatical scrapbook contents, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 730)
        Includes photographs, brochures, and diary entries documenting the Wilders' travels through The Netherlands, Belgium, and Germany.
      - Florence and Near East scrapbooks, 1959 (Box 55)
      - Germany and Near East scrapbook, 1958 (Box 56)
      - Germany and Near East scrapbook, 1959 (Box 392)
      - Strasbourg, Germany scrapbook, 1958 (Box 57)
      - Strasbourg, Germany scrapbook, 1960 (Box 393)
      - Sabbatical scrapbook, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 747-748)
        Includes photographs from the Wilders' travels in Switzerland, The Netherlands, Germany, France, and other European countries. Also includes photographs from Blue Hill, Maine.
      - Sabbatical scrapbook, 1958–1959 (Box 58, Folder 749)
        Includes photographs from Strasbourg, Florence, Damascus, and Bethlehem.
      - Sabbatical scrapbook, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 750)
        Includes photographs from Basel, Switzerland.
      - Sabbatical scrapbook, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 751-753)
        The scrapbook was received in poor condition and therefore the scrapbook was separated into folders to ensure preservation.
      - Scrapbook covers, circa 1959-1966 (Box 60)
        Includes covers from the Blue Hill Maine, Sabbatical 1959, Claremont, New Harmony, Rice, and European Sabbatical 1966 scrapbooks.
      - Scrapbook covers, circa 1959-1966 (Box 61)
      - Scandinavia trip materials, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 754-758)
        Includes diary entries, brochures, and photographs from the Wilders' travels in Scandinavia.
      - Southern France scrapbook, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 759-760, Box 62, Folder 760a)
        Includes diary entries, brochures, and photographs from the Wilders' travels in Southern France.
      - St. Petersburg, Florida materials, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 761-762)
        Includes diary entries and postcards from the Wilders' visit to St. Petersburg, Florida.
      - Switzerland, Italy, Alps, and Prague scrapbook, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 763)
      - Wilder family photographs, 1889–1942 (Box 62, Folder 764)
        Includes photographs and printed information about Joseph Wilder. Also includes a photograph of Catharine Kerlin Wilder and her children.
  - Career related materials, 1902–1992
    - Das Edle Blut Wildenbruch, 1902 (Box 63, Folder 765)
      Book written by C.A. Eggert with an inscription "L.T. O'Connor 49 Canyon Road Berkeley, California".
    - Theophilus in New York, undated (Box 63, Folder 766)
      Typescript copy of a potential sequel to Thornton Wilder's book, Theophilus North.
    - Wilder, Amos Tappan correspondence, 1980–1989 (Box 63, Folder 767-770)
      Includes thank you notes from guests at Isabel's 80th birthday party which Tappan collected and mailed to his parents. Also includes Tappan correspondence to his parents.
    - Wilder, Catharine Dix correspondence, 1956–1989 (Box 63, Folder 771-779)
      Catharine Dix Wilder's clippings and correspondence sent to her parents.
    - Wilder, Isabel correspondence, 1955–1992 (Box 63, Folder 780-782, Box 64, Folder 783-786)
    - Isabel Wilder reel, undated (Box 64, Folder 787)
    - Agendas, 1943–1984 (Box 64, Folder 788-795, Box 65, Folder 796-800)
      Pocket agendas arranged in chronological order.
    - Oberlin honorary degree, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 801)
    - Medals, circa 1960 (Box 66, Folder 815-818)
      Includes one Belgian centennial media, circa 1930, one championship winner medal from the United States Lawn Association, Deschamps medal, and a Wilbur Lucius cross medal from the Yale Graduate School Association.
    - Letter box contents, 1926–1934 (Box 65, Folder 802-809)
      Includes postcards, pamphlets, and letters saved by Amos in a letter box in alphabetical order. Most postcards are written by Amos to Catharine but some included postcards are written by other family members. Some postcards are blank. Also includes travelers' guides to Oxford and Rome. One letter box has been saved as an example of how Amos saved and organized some of his correspondence and files.
    - Letter box, 1926–1934 (Box 67)
    - Deconstruction notes, 1981–1988 (Box 65, Folder 810-812)
    - Photographs
      - Conference photographs, circa 1931 (Box 65, Folder 813)
        Includes photographs taken at conferences in Maine and Amsterdam, the Netherlands.
      - Europe photographs, undated (Box 65, Folder 814)
      - Miscellaneous photographs of people, 1915–1933 (Box 68, Folder 819)
      - Miscellaneous photographs of people and landscapes, undated (Box 68, Folder 820)
        The landscape photographs are potentially taken in the United States and Europe.
      - Miscellaneous photographs, 1974–1975 (Box 68, Folder 821)
      - Miscellaneous photographs, circa 1919 (Box 68, Folder 822-823)
        Includes photographs of Amos and his army unit.
      - Miscellaneous photographs, Marsailles, France, undated (Box 68, Folder 824)
        Includes photographs and negatives developed in Marseilles, France.
      - Miscellaneous photographs, the University of California, Berkeley, circa 1937 (Box 68, Folder 825)
      - Miscellaneous family photographs, circa 1939 (Box 68, Folder 826)
      - Tennis photograph, undated (Box 69, Folder 835)
      - Travel photographs and negatives, circa 1916-1969 (Box 68, Folder 827-832, Box 70, Folder 836-839)
        Includes prints and negatives from the Wilder family home in Blue Hill, Maine and Amos's travels in Europe and India.
      - Postcards, undated (Box 70, Folder 840)
        Includes blank souvenir postcards Amos saved including a postcard set from the White Mountains in New Hampshire.
      - Wilder, Amos Niven photographs, circa 1951-1954 (Box 70, Folder 841)
        Includes photographs of Amos Niven and potentially Amos Parker.
      - World War I photographs, circa 1917 (Box 70, Folder 842)
      - Life Magazine photograph, circa 1955 (Box 71, Folder 854)
      - Thacher School photograph, circa 1911-1912 (Box 71, Folder 855)
      - Postcards and a map of the Rhine, circa 1923-1925 (Box 72, Folder 860-863)
        Includes blank postcards and a relief-panorama map of the Rhine.
    - Writings and notes
      - Frye, Northrup notes, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 843)
      - The Gospel of Luke and Acts notes and writings, 1961–1966 (Box 70, Folder 844)
      - The Gospel of Mark notes and writings, 1956–1966 (Box 70, Folder 845)
        Includes notes, pamphlets, and writings on the Gospel of Mark.
      - The Gospel of Matthew notes and writings, 1958–1967 (Box 70, Folder 846)
      - Gospel Theology notes and writings, circa 1965 (Box 70, Folder 847-848)
      - Hebrews writings, circa 1948 (Box 70, Folder 849)
      - Jones, David catalog, circa 1972 (Box 70, Folder 850)
        Includes correspondence from Tony Stoneburner.
      - Poetry files, 1966–1991 (Box 70, Folder 851)
        Includes "The Book of Job's Wife" by Norma Farber and "Remembrance and the Poet: Gadamer on Holderlin" presented at the Modern Language Association in Chicago in 1990 as well as a flyer from the Religion and Non-Religion in Contemporary Poetry by Robert Lowell event held at Harvard Divinity School.
      - Poetry group, circa 1948 (Box 70, Folder 852)
        Includes files from the poetry group Amos belonged to in Chicago.
      - Positions by Jacques Derrida, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 853)
        Includes an annotated copy of Positions. Also includes typescript writings by Amos.
      - Jacques Derrida notes, undated (Box 73, Folder 864)
      - Franz Kneisel notes, 1962–1978 (Box 73, Folder 865)
      - Schweitzer, Albert international colloquium materials and correspondence, 1942–1990 (Box 73, Folder 866-867)
    - Wilder, Isabella correspondence, 1913–1920 (Box 73, Folder 868)
    - Auden, W.H. correspondence, 1941–1982 (Box 73, Folder 869)
    - Thacher School correspondence, 1911–1914 (Box 73, Folder 870)
    - Freedman Dramatic Agency correspondence, 1987 March (Box 73, Folder 871)
    - King, Henry, 1914 (Box 73, Folder 872)
    - Wilder, Amos Parker correspondence, 1914–1915 (Box 73, Folder 873)
    - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence, 1916 (Box 73, Folder 874)
    - Toulouse Montauban materials, 1919 (Box 73, Folder 875)
    - Summer after discharge materials, 1919 (Box 73, Folder 876)
    - Brussels, Belgium materials, 1921 (Box 73, Folder 877)
    - Oxford materials, 1919–1923 (Box 73, Folder 878-879)
    - Travel year materials, 1924–1925 (Box 73, Folder 880)
    - Travels with Ward Terry and Warwick Bausal materials, 1924–1925 (Box 73, Folder 881)
    - Autographed letters, 1938–1980 (Box 73, Folder 882-883)
      Includes letters from Kingman Brewster, Ezra Pound, and George MacLeod among others.
    - North Conway photographs and clippings, 1925–1928 (Box 73, Folder 884)
    - Chicago Theological Seminary, 1943–1944 (Box 73, Folder 885)
      Includes programs from the Service of Inauguration and Dedication and the Chicago Theological Seminary Register.
    - Sabbatical in Strasbourg, 1958–1959 (Box 74, Folder 886)
      Includes materials from Amos' sabbatical in France.
    - Berkeley, California materials, 1909 (Box 74, Folder 887)
      Includes a program from the Mc Kinley School Christmas event.
    - Yale crosswalk, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 888)
      Includes correspondence and writings related to the presentation of a crosswalk on the Yale campus.
    - Family correspondence, notes, and clippings, circa 1924-1980 (Box 74, Folder 889, Box 75, Folder 908-914, Box 76, Folder 915-923, Box 77, Folder 924-930)
      Includes typed family genealogy, clippings about family members including Janet and Isabel, and correspondence written by Amos to his mother and other family members.
    - Correspondence and writings, 1969–1982 (Box 74, Folder 890)
      Includes correspondence from Tony Stoneburner and Frances Crosby. Includes typescript writings by Amos entitled "Me Go to Hong Kong", "Kingman Brewster- A Few Reminiscences", and a copy of layouts for First Printings of American Authors.
  - Charlotte T. Niven materials, 1901–1979
    - Address book (Box 74, Folder 891-892)
    - Clippings, circa 1922 (Box 74, Folder 893)
      Also includes Charlotte Niven's bookplate, artwork, and a journal article.
    - General correspondence, 1901–1974 (Box 74, Folder 894-897)
    - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence, circa 1979 (Box 74, Folder 898)
    - Wilder, Catharine Dix correspondence, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 899)
    - Wilder, Charlotte correspondence, circa 1973 (Box 74, Folder 900)
      Includes an embroidered handkerchief.
    - Finances and notes, 1972–1979 (Box 74, Folder 901)
      Includes financial documents, correspondence, and materials relating to Charlotte's care and funeral services.
    - Miscellaneous family files, undated (Box 74, Folder 902)
      Includes a birthday candle and a photocopy of an article written about Amos Todd Wilder.
    - Guardianship materials, 1974–1979 (Box 74, Folder 903-907)
      Includes materials relating to Catharine and Amos's guardianship of Amos's aunt Charlotte.
    - Journal, undated (Box 78, Folder 931-932)
    - Notes, 1922–1948 (Box 78, Folder 933-934)
      Includes handwritten and typescripts of various notes and articles and some materials from the Y.W.C.A.
    - Photocopied materials, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 935-936)
      Includes photocopies of article and journal entries as well as a photocopied last will and testament.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 78, Folder 937)
    - Travel journal entries and fragments, 1921–1945 (Box 78, Folder 938)
      Includes typed transcript copies of journal entries written during Charlotte's travels to New Zealand, Japan, Australia, and Palestine.
  - Printed materials, 1941–1984
    - The Kenyon Review
      The Kenyon Reviews were received in 2001. There were 91 copies in all. The issues that have been retained have significant annotations. The library contains every issue of the Kenyon reviews that was accessioned with the collection. [provide link to Orbis record of Kenyon reviews?]
      - The Kenyon Review, Winter 1941 (Box 78, Folder 939)
      - The Kenyon Review, Summer 1943 (Box 78, Folder 940)
      - The Kenyon Review, Autumn 1943 (Box 78, Folder 941)
      - The Kenyon Review, Winter 1944 (Box 79, Folder 942)
      - The Kenyon Review, Autumn 1946 (Box 79, Folder 943)
      - Enclosures from The Kenyon Review, Summer 1948 (Box 79, Folder 944)
      - Enclosures from The Kenyon Review, Spring 1951 (Box 79, Folder 945)
      - Enclosures from The Kenyon Review, Spring 1952 (Box 79, Folder 946)